Here we relax.
For those of you born in the 60-70s, remember this children's program.
The TV has lighting so it lights up a nice black and white image in the evening.
I got these furniture from a colleague's parents.
They are nice to have on the ice so we took them.
Speed Weekend also has a prize for best depot and there we have been high for many years.
Both one and two, so we hope for a profit.
-It's a lot of noise.
There is a lot of sound.
It belongs well, I guess.
We sit in here instead because it sounds so much outside.
There are so many who do noise all the time.
We peeled up the engine a bit.
It is an iterative process.
What is most critical this time?
Then we will get it.
Do you see that guy Douglas?
The engine geek guy in blue pants.
You should follow that guy on Youtube.
Now it is the black hole that is going out and driving.
Wondering if anyone has talked about it being a bump in the ice at the end of the track?
The black hole aims to drive faster than last year.
Which was 241 km/h on average.
Keep your ears good people.
Holy Baloney!
Totally amazing!
Did you kiss on you?
Hahahaha!